{
    "id": "7bec0df7d6d746f69d0511a870d1a937",
    "title": "Compound And Complex Sentence",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The doctor must come at once ............................................... the patient will die.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "if",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c383fdba271a40c784971646d77f6069"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. the doctor does not come at once, the patient will die.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2d626af71a54b3ba014c0ba43e1f6e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gandhi believed in non-violence ........................................... some of his followers were extremists.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b7377c5ce1aa456ebf0325dae87f5278"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... Gandhi believed in non-violence some of his followers were extremists.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23de2c79282949e48570d16136d5cd3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Search his pockets .................................................. you will find the stolen watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "and",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4be6ccb990914e0abd073cd569f9ff94"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................................... you search his pockets, you will find the stolen watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "16518ebded984038b12cd9a01fdfde60"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must hurry .............................................. you will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a66e3944a86e463babc4475f0f416ae4"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ you do not hurry you will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "709cfe8656004f329ccff7166aebef28"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wants to be a scholar, ........................................... he is studying hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "therefore",
                "hence",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8557edcd262f4192a2ddcf415afbc7e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................... he wants to be a scholar he is studying hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "864e096d0bc74151a0e0ab904432c2e1"
        }
    ]
}